易考范文三十五
With the development of society,
people have to face all aspects of pressure
that comes from family and society,
from study and work. Therefore,
keeping a good mood becomes more and more important,
no matter what situation we are in.
In the first place,
a good mood enables you to keep healthy.
A good mood helps us to be optimistic towards everything,
and therefore reduces the possibility of getting ill.
At the same time it increases
the possibility of recovering from illness.
In the second place, a good mood enables us
to study or work efficiently.
Stress is a natural part of daily life
and there is no way to avoid it,
but a good mood helps develop our adaptive abilities
to deal well with it rather than escape from it.
Based on the above reasons,
we can safely come to the conclusion that
it is important to keep a good mood in our daily life.
It can benefit both our health
and our efficiency of work and study.
If you are not keeping a good mood,
just start to improve now.